Hi, I'm Manu Mendez.

IRATA LEVEL 3 & NDT LEVEL 2 | BLADE INSPECTION & REPAIR | GWO BLADE REPAIR / BST /BST SEA SURVIVAL CERTIFIED | CONFINED SPACE | WINDA ID:MM010834IN

↓ +917356096369
manumendezgomez99@gmail.com

INDIA

SUMMARY

An organized self-starter, proactive, dedicated and strong decision maker having 9 years of experience in IRATA Level 3 (Oil & Gas Industry, Structural Engineering, Membrane Installation). Believes continuing education is essential to keeping up with latest technology and sharing of knowledge with colleagues in addition to bettering their abilities to serve the organization.

SKILLS

- · Quality Assurance
- Rigging Operations
- · Team Building

Equipment Inspection

Training Coordination

EXPERIENCE

Rope Access Supervisor

06/2022 - 04/2024

A star Testing Singapore, Singapore

- Supervised Level 2&1 Technicians in NDT, Inspection, Rigging, RT, DRT
- · Provided on-site engineering and technical services during installation and NDT processes
- Accountable for safety performance in responsible area
- Supervised insulation and operation of Piping
- · Estimated project costs and resource allocation to forecast budget requirements and monitor adherence.
- Built work schedules and staff assignments, taking workload, space and equipment availability into consideration.

Rope Access Supervisor

12/2021 - 04/2022

Mekanchi Global Private Limited India

- · Telephone tower Structure maintenance Bolt Torquing and
- Provided on-site engineering and technical services during installation and
- NDT processes
- Accountable for safety performance in responsible area

Level 3 Supervisor

08/2021 - 12/2021

MIRACULOUS GROUP Delhi, India

- Supervising NDT Operations
- Supervised safety in work place

Level 2 Technician

05/2018 - 04/2020

Hightex GmbH Doha, Qatar

Level 1 & 2 Membrane Technician PTFE, ETFE & PVC

- · Installation and maintenance of Structural & Membrane
- Provided on-site engineering and technical services during installation
- · Accountable for safety performance in responsible area.

Level 1 Technician 04/2016 - 08/2017

Taiyo Middle East LLC Doha, Qatar

Membrane Technician

- PTFE.ETFE & PVC
- Installation and maintenance of Structural & Membrane
- · Accountable for safety performance in responsible area

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

High School Diploma Vettucaud HSS, Kerala 04/2008

CERTIFICATIONS

IRATA LEVEL 3 & NDT LEVEL 2 | BLADE INSPECTION & REPAIR | GWO BLADE REPAIR /BST /BST SEA SURVIVAL CERTIFIED | CONFINED SPACE | WINDA ID:MM010834IN